Joseph A. Butler

9042 Lorton Station Blvd, Lorton, Virginia 22079 Cell: (703) 508-8295

Email: Butlerjoseph25@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/butlerjoseph

Career Profile

Customer Success professional with extensive experience in technology and account management. Passion for building strong relationships with clients. Expert with data, and client on-boarding, which includes customer retention and providing top of the line client service. Fast learner who can become an expert in any product/service or learn any system/software.

Professional Experience

InLoop Inc., Remote/Alexandria, Virginia

Customer Success Manager, July 2018 – Present

- Manages all US clients (Associations)
- Monitor client usage and based on statistics, suggest recommended strategies to improve and utilize AI feature better
- Customer advocate for clients when communicating to global technology and R&D teams
- •Onboard clients and manage them from start to finish after sale is closed
- •Train clients on software via ZOOM, previously GoToMeeting
- Made adjustments to onboarding process and client outreach. to make it quicker, more efficient, and to be proactive

Goodzer Inc., Reston, Virginia

Customer Success Manager, Mar 2016 - July 2018

- First and most Senior Customer Success Manager at Goodzer
- Exceeded monthly quota for onboarding accounts and client retention, every month since I have been hired
- Manage over 100 paid accounts, and 30+ onboarding accounts
- Implement new processes and best practices which makes onboarding and retention easier and more clear
- Customer Advocate for all accounts, as I speak to owners and senior decision makers everyday
- Trains new Customer Success Managers as they come on board

CPA Global, Alexandria, Virginia

Client Service Specialist, Dec 2014 – Mar 2016

- Managed day to day queries for 20 KEY clients via phone, and email
- Manage any projects assigned to me from start to finish, and ensure internal and external clients are kept in the loop through constant communication
- Analyzed client's data and successfully implemented over 30 projects for our patents team in the span of 3 months
- 98% client satisfaction for our 24-hour SLA policy
- Utilized proprietary ECM system daily, to manage workflow and processes
- Trained new hires on ECM processes and policies

Education Summary

- University of Minnesota, Bachelor of Science Entrepreneurship (2019 Grad)
- Vermilion Community College, Associates Degree in Liberal Arts (IT concentration)